[
  {
    "index": 0,
    "question": "🛏️+😳+L",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "SOCIAL"
  },
  {
    "index": 1,
    "question": "✒️+🤥+SH",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "ENGLISH"
  },
  {
    "index": 2,
    "question": " 💵+😷+CS",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "MATHEMATICS"
  },
  {
    "index": 3,
    "question": "🐓+D",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "HINDI"
  },
  {
    "index": 4,
    "question": "SIN+C",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "SCIENCE"
  },
  {
    "index": 5,
    "question": "©+🙎‍♂️+🌳",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "CHEMISTRY"
  },
  {
    "index": 6,
    "question": "🐍+🌲",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "HISTORY"
  },
  {
    "index": 7,
    "question": "📲+❄️+🇺🇸",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "CALCULUS"
  },
  {
    "index": 8,
    "question": " 🥇+⌚+🎙️+S",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "ECONOMICS"
  },
  {
    "index": 9,
    "question": "GO+📊",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "GEOGRAPHY"

}
  
  
]